[♪ opening theme song playing]
DAEMONS OF THE SHADOW REALM
[Right yells]
[Ivan grunts]
[Danji (Tsugai) screams]
[LEFT] Right.
What's wrong?
-He has done something bad.
-[RIGHT] Huh?
Get out of my way, Right!
I told you,
Lady Left's head is mine!
[RIGHT] Huh?
[Ivan grunts]
[grunts]
[gasps]
♪
[Ivan grunting]
[gasps] Bastard!
I hit his leg!
How is he so agile?
[Yuru grunting]
[Right grunts]
Dera! Shoot now!
[Yuru grunts]
[DERA] Yuru!
-[LEFT] Uh?
-[Right grunts]
-[RIGHT] Yuru!
-It's just a scratch!
-I can still fight.
-You mustn't move.
-Stay down!
-So close.
[gasps, grunts]
You're kidding.
This guy can redirect bullets?
Damn, he disappeared.
[groaning]
[GUARD] That's right,
the warehouse is full of blood.
Oh, crap, it's a nightmare.
Corpses everywhere.
At least five, maybe 10 dead?
-How should I know?
-[footsteps]
I'm not going in
to count their heads.
Send someone as fast as you can.
[IVAN] Well, great.
[sighs] She hasn't gotten here
to clean up the bodies yet.
-[grunts softly]
-Huh? Who're you? No!
Buddy! Stop!
You can't go in there!
I just called the cops and...
Wait, did you do this?
Uh, yeah, so...
I just saw a man teleport.
[DISPATCHER] What? I...
Sir, are you sure you're okay?
Take a deep breath!
EPISODE 20
THE HUNTED AND THE HUNTER
[Bow-Legs and Pigeon-Toes
whimper]
[PIGEON-TOES] Help! Help!
[SHINGO]
Your daemons control people?
That's one hell
of a messed up pair.
Since you came for the boy,
I'm guessing you're with
Higashi Village, that right?
[bandit grunts]
[Shingo grunts]
Hey, you two. Keep a tight grip
on our new friends here.
I ain't about to let 'em
hijack my body.
There's a group of people
gathering on the street outside.
[Shingo grunts]
They probably sent
some more of our guys
to check on me,
since my phone's broke.
I don't like that the Kagemoris
brought Asa, though.
We should bounce
before they take our daemons.
[ASUMA] Yes, agreed.
My father would have my head
if he discovered I've been
acting as a spy on your behalf.
The only way to ensure
he doesn't find out
-is to kill this man.
-[gasps, trembles]
Be my guest.
[Pigeon-Toes
and Bow-Legs whimper]
[BOTH]
No! Please don't hurt him!
No, hold on,
I'll keep my mouth shut.
I swear I will. [trembles]
Try not to make a mess,
will you?
Blood's a pain to clean up.
I'm begging you!
Can't we cut some kind of deal?
-[ASUMA] Sorry, no.
-I'll do anything.
Come to think of it,
ain't this your first murder?
[ASUMA] That's correct.
Though he's not the one
I wish to kill.
[SHINGO] Uh?
[gasps]
[Shingo gasps, grunts]
[ASUMA]
Stay where you are, daemons.
I couldn't show my hand before
because you were perched
on the old man's shoulders.
But my moment has arrived.
Aw. Shocked?
I've waited such a long time
for the opportunity
to kill you myself,
dearest uncle.
Kill me?
Fujin! Raijin! What the hell?
Didn't you sense anything?
Yozakura's ability
to conceal their presence
and bloodlust are unmatched.
[YOZAKURA] Gonzo, Asa,
and Fuyuki are nearby.
I expect they'll arrive
here shortly.
What? It can talk?
You're not going to die yet.
We still have
a wealth of information
to extract from you.
[grunts] Fujin!
Blow Yozakura away!
[YOZAKURA]
I would snap your neck
before the breeze
even began to stir.
Of course, if you try lightning,
you'll be electrocuted as well.
What will it be, daemons?
A move against me
will seal your master's fate,
and you'll watch him die
in Yozakura's capable talons.
So, um... Who's on whose team?
[SHINGO] You traitor.
You would pull this
after everything
I've invested in you?
Poor fool. Listen to you.
You use your money
to control people
and you're surprised
when it doesn't buy you
-true loyalty.
-[Shingo grunts]
Consider this... What is a clan?
A collection of people
united by something.
Those of the Kagemori clan,
servants included,
were rejected because the world
and others viewed us
as useless, different,
and strange.
They accepted my mother
after the Shingos
treated her terribly.
They gave her a home,
a place to belong.
You're also family,
but I cannot forgive you.
I never had any intention
of letting you use
the twins' power.
Certainly not to destroy
those who saved my mother.
That said, you're not
the only one who has designs
on the Kagemori clan, are you?
[Shingo grunting]
[ASUMA] It takes more than
one arrogant old man
to crush such an organization.
Listen well. Your future depends
on how you answer this question.
Somebody has been
guiding your hand.
Who are they?
[Shingo breathes shakily]
What's this?
Hey, Ivan! Perfect timing!
Kill this guy!
Ah, damn, I see what's going on.
I told you not to underestimate
your nephew.
Obviously, you didn't take
my advice to heart.
Not the time! Gonzo, Asa,
and Fuyuki are here, too!
If they catch us, we're screwed!
[sword slashes]
Yeah, that's true.
[Shingo and Yozakura groaning]
No! Yozakura!
[sword slashes]
[IVAN]
If Fuyuki's daemons get you,
they'll learn all
the information in your head.
Can't let that happen.
Be straight with me, Asuma.
[Asuma breathes shakily]
I want to know everything
Shingo told you.
[Asuma breathes uneasily]
DAEMONS OF THE SHADOW REALM
[DERA] Crap!
That's not a scratch, damn it!
Man, this is bad.
If you show up at a hospital
with a gunshot wound,
they'll have
a ton of questions for you.
Hana is not gonna be happy.
[grunts] That hurts!
I'm sorry. I didn't know
we were dealing with someone
who could deflect rifle bullets
with his swords.
It's fine. None of us
could've known.
This wasn't your fault at all.
So was that trick something
his daemons allowed him to do,
or is he good enough to have
honed those skills himself?
Likely a combination of the two.
Daemons aiding
a master swordsman.
Well then, they're extremely
compatible with each other.
In any event,
it's bad news for us.
That guy was able
to hold his own
while fighting both of you
at the same time.
Oh! Hold on.
Danji! How do you fare?
Hello?
[Danji (Tsugai) gasps]
I'm alive! Where the heck is he?
[RIGHT] He got away.
You mind grabbing my leg
while you're down there?
I almost forgot
he injured you, too.
What can we do to fix you up?
[RIGHT] It's nothing for you
to worry about.
Just a minor wound
like Left's arm.
We should be as good
as new in no time
once you've purchased
a strong adhesive for us.
You say that, but the guy
also stabbed you in the heart.
[LEFT] Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not human.
I don't have a heart.
What? By that logic,
would you even survive
a headshot?
[LEFT] Likely.
Is there any injury
that would kill you?
-That would kill us?
-[BOTH] Hm?
We've never died before,
so we don't know.
Okay, yeah, fair point.
[LEFT] We don't understand
death.
But his attack
was nothing to scoff at.
Completely drained my stamina
in an instant.
What kind of ability was that?
Since it KO'd Left and seemed
to kick-start the pervert,
my best guess is
some kind of power transference?
KO'd? Kick-started?
[DERA] Like a vampire. Hm.
He was thirsty for energy.
Whatever the case,
I'll be immobile for a while.
The gun is useless against him,
and these two are missing limbs.
We've been taken off the board.
Let's leave them
to the Kagemoris.
Forgive us, Yuru.
We failed you.
He was the best lead you had
on your parents,
and we let him escape.
No, I'm the one
who should apologize.
You fought so hard on my behalf
and look at the toll it took
on your bodies.
Our current master
has such a deep well of kindness
within him
-that it sometimes seems unreal.
-Hm. Hm.
[YURU] Seriously?
What the heck was your
previous master like anyway?
[grunts] The pervert may have
gotten away this eve.
But we know the scent
of his blood now.
He won't escape again.
Does that mean the two of you
are sticking it out with me?
Of course we are!
Don't you understand?
We'll always be by your side,
Master Yuru!
That wasn't
terribly nice of you.
I was hoping that I would get
the chance to kill him myself.
[grunts] I'm sorry, buddy.
Guess I saved you
the trouble, didn't I?
Just think,
making a dead body's easy,
but cleaning one up sure isn't.
Why get your own hands dirty
when it's easier
to just leave it
to the pros like me?
I question the integrity
of advice
given by a man
who would cut down
their own employer so easily.
You say that like I was
supposed to have
some special attachment
to Shingo.
He was a paycheck.
And all that blood and sweat
I put in for him
more than earned my rate.
So you silenced him.
I don't suppose he told you
anything before he died?
No. You got to him
before he talked.
Though I don't believe my uncle
could have done this
without someone else
whispering into his ear.
And given how fast
you were to put him down,
I suspect you know who that was.
[Ivan sighs]
♪
[trembling]
[Ivan grunts]
[Asuma breathes shakily]
I'm dead.
[Asuma grunts]
[Ivan grunts]
[grunting]
♪
[Ivan breathing heavily]
[groans] Holy crap.
Left's energy
felt great at first. [grunts]
But that kickback is killer.
-[grunting]
-[DAIKYO] Ivan...
They're here.
The dangerous people.
-[Ivan grunts]
-[MAN 1] Who's this old man?
[man 2 gasps] The Kagemoris!
[screaming]
[Shokyo grunts] I'm sensing
a veritable feast
of daemons here!
Let's take their master's energy
and start another bloodbath!
[IVAN] Nope, not happening
on this leg.
[SHOKYO] From the brat's arrow?
I told you,
just heal it back up!
[IVAN] I'll remind you
this is a fresh wound
on top of where
you already stabbed me, idiot.
[SHOKYO]
Oh! That gives me an idea!
If I stab your other leg,
that will restore
your body's balance!
Then you can run around again!
[Ivan sighs]
You're never gonna understand
just how frail humans are.
-It's your lucky day, Mr. Asuma.
-[footsteps]
[Ivan groans]
Don't really feel like
dying today,
so it's about time I head out.
Besides, aren't you ready
to go back home?
We wouldn't want something bad
to happen to Yozakura, would we?
Ta-ta.
-[sword whooshes]
-[glass shatters]
[groans]
♪
[Ivan grunts]
[door opens]
Whoa! This is quite the scene!
What happened here?
[gasps] Asuma, your arm!
Is the cut serious, son?
[ASUMA] Forgive me, Father.
I failed to capture
my uncle alive.
Oh, Shingo.
Were you the one who did him in?
[ASUMA] No.
There was a falling out.
Or rather,
they didn't want him talking.
This is the doing
of Ivan Yosano.
Yosano? I recall you told us
about a Daemon Wielder
Shingo recently hired
with dual katanas.
[Asa gasps]
Sir, there was a man outside
with katanas!
I should have used Break
to try to capture him.
My apologies, Fuyuki.
Not even the relics remain
of his daemons.
You can't extract anything.
I learned my uncle had
someone behind the scenes
who was feeding him information,
but he died
before I found out who.
I have failed.
You shouldn't concern yourself
with that in your present state.
Let's stop your bleeding.
[Asuma gasps]
The man from Higashi Village
we captured got away, too.
[Bow-Legs and Pigeon-Toes
squealing]
[line ringing]
[WOMAN] Hey, hey, hey, hey!
How's my big ol' cutie doing?
[Ivan sighs]
[IVAN] Mineyama, where are you?
At the warehouse, duh!
[IVAN] The bodies were
still there a minute ago.
Hurry up and do your job.
[MINEYAMA] Aw, I'm so sorry
for being late!
I mean, this place is so big.
I got lost!
But no worries,
I'm taking care of it right now!
Come on, I already said
I was sorry, didn't I?
I mean, I can't help it
if my cram school
lets me out late.
And, like, you killed
so many people.
It's a lot of work to clean
all that up for you.
Of course, my pair
is always delighted to do it!
Huh?
Are you telling me
every one of these people
was from Higashi Village?
I've never fed my buddies
mountain meat before.
Anyway, where can I find you
when I'm finished up?
There!
Job well done.
♪
Uh?
-[whimpering]
-What's wrong, mister?
If you're starting
to see weird things,
it's probably
'cause you're tired.
You should go home and sleep.
[whimpering]
♪
[officer 1 sighs] The call said
there was a massacre
in this warehouse, right?
I mean, forget bodies.
I don't even see
a drop of blood.
Me neither.
Uh?
Whoa, there's a hole
in the roof.
[OFFICER 1] What the hell?
We've been trying
for a few minutes,
but we can't get him
to calm down.
[GUARD] But I... I saw it.
[cries]
Relax, sir. We're just trying
to understand, 'kay?
[GUARD] You don't get it!
You guys think I'm crazy!
But I saw it!
They were all dead.
Then a young girl showed up.
She rolled up all the bodies
into a ball and left.
[OFFICER] Uh...
[guard cries]
Just tell me, officers,
have I really
gone off the deep end after all?
[cries]
[footsteps]
[MINEYAMA] Oh, Master Ivan!
Ivan, sweetie!
Mm? [chuckles]
There you are!
Guess who's here?
Ugh, don't yell.
My head is killing me.
Be still, my heart!
The big strong man
needs my help!
[SHOKYO] Ivan, can I kill her?
[IVAN] For once, we feel
the same way, Shokyo.
Oh, did you do the life energy
transfer thing?
Yeah. I tried to recover
a bit off of Left.
Whoa! You drained
a freakin' god!
Bet that felt wild.
Yeah. It feels like
I went and chugged
a bucket full of energy drinks
all at once.
Ah, crap.
The strain on my heart
is getting to be too much.
[grunts] I'll be out of action
for a while.
Wait, if you can't move,
then this is my chance!
Don't worry yourself!
I'm ready to give you
mouth to mouth! [panting]
-Back off, pervert.
-[chuckles excitedly]
Yeah, or what?
You couldn't even beat Left
let alone kill Yuru,
so you have got nothing
to show for your efforts.
Don't be so sure.
Yuru's gonna come after me.
I'll get my second chance
before long.
Aw, sounds like the two of you
are in love!
Be careful or I'll get jealous.
Well, good luck out there.
You'd better stay safe,
'cause I'd just hate
to have to bring you back to
Nishino Village as a meatball!
[ASA] Brother...
[whimpers]
You got shot?
Yeah. Dera shot my shoulder
with his "rifle" thingy.
I'll kill you, Dera!
Context! Give her the context!
[ASA] I distinctly remember
back at the manor,
you said you'd take care of him!
[DERA] I'm sorry! Really, I am!
[ASA] And you're no better!
What're all those muscles for
if you can't keep
my brother safe?
-Fair point.
-Apologies.
[ASA] Oh, I knew it.
The Kagemoris should've
taken him in after all!
We can't trust Higashi Village!
Just look at this lineup
you had!
Three powerhouses, and you still
couldn't protect Yuru!
-And as for you!
-[gasps]
I'm so sorry.
[Asa sighs softly]
♪
[both breathe uneasily]
[ASA] I'll let you out
when I'm done working.
[ASA (FAKE)] How long
have we been trapped in here?
[gasps]
Huh? Where'd she go?
Wait. Does this mean
she's letting us out?
[Asa (fake) gasps]
Brother.
You're here.
[AZAMI] Uh? [whimpers]
Who are you?
-[DERA] Hey! Azami.
-Uh?
-Glad you're all right, kiddo.
-[AZAMI] Huh?
Oh! Mr. Dera?
What happened to your beard?
And, um... What is this place?
[cries] Nothing here
makes any sense to me!
Please, can I go back home?
Try to relax, young lady.
It's fine.
Those scary men
aren't here anymore.
Get away! You're scary, too!
I can tell
your smile isn't real!
-[Azami cries]
-[Gonzo sighs]
[RIGHT] Come now,
calm down, lass!
We're here to make sure
you stay safe!
[AZAMI] Huh?
Uh...
Oh, right. I forgot,
you can't see us.
Remember from before?
We had met in Higashi Village!
[AZAMI] Uh?
[squeaks]
[thuds]
Uh-oh. She has lost
consciousness again.
Still kinda hurts, you know!
Hold on. If Azami's the only one
who came out,
then inside, Yuru, Danji
and both Asas are duking it out.
That won't be pretty.
[♪ closing theme song playing]
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
[ASA (FAKE)] I'm so sorry.
It was wrong. I knew that,
but I kept doing it.
[KYOKA] In the face
of unimaginable power,
people lose their humanity.
EPISODE 21: ZASHIKI-WARASHI
AND HIGASHI VILLAGE